# ABIGAIL LIMPIOSO

Orlando, FL 32825 • 954-756-3916 • alimpiosowork@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/alimpioso ● GitHub.com/AbbyNeko ● abbyneko.github.io

# **Summary**

Full-Stack Web Developer with more than 3 years of programming experience working with well-known brands and companies. Designing solutions and delivering to clients in a timely manner. Adept problem solving ability and eager to take on new challenges. Collaborated with third party companies by providing consultation and scripting solutions based on client needs. Certified in Full-Stack Web Development, achieving an A in the overall course.

# **Experience**

### **Front-End Developer**

eMerge Technologies

February 2017 - present

- Advanced skills in JavaScript and adapted to meet the demands of clients in need of API Integration solutions
- Built and rigorously tested user interfaces to ensure a functional and user-friendly design
- Maintained the eMerge Technologies WordPress site by creating or editing pages using HTML, CSS and PHP
- Interacted directly with clients to assess issues and develop out-of-the-box scripting solutions to fit the unique needs of each client

### **Production Assistant/Print Designer**

The Spot @ UCF

Dec 2015 - March 2017

- Delivered excellent customer service when assisting customers with printing and retail transactions
- Trained and directed new employees on imperative company policies and procedures
- Collaborated with co-workers to complete print projects within given deadlines
- Designed business cards and signs for the store using Adobe Illustrator and Photoshop

### Web/Graphic Design Intern (Remote)

**Give Back Nation** 

Aug 2016 - February 2017

- Produced graphics and web pages to modernize the site for the non-profit company Give Back Nation
- Improved SEO and marketability of their site by making web pages responsive

### **Education**

### **Full-Stack Web Development Certificate**

University of Central Florida 2020

Orlando, FL

### **Bachelors of the Arts, Digital Media**

University of Central Florida 2012 - 2016

**GPA: 3.5** Orlando, FL

### **Honors & Awards**

**Dean's List** Fall & Spring 2015

**President's Honor Roll** Spring 2016

### **Technical Skills**

HTML Git Node.js

CSS Adobe Illustrator API Development

JavaScript Adobe Photoshop Express

AJAX React MongoDB

jQuery Bootstrap PHP

# **Projects**

**Weather Dashboard** is an app that displays today's weather data by city and saving each search to the side.

#### **Languages Used:**

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Open Weather API

#### GitHub:

https://github.com/AbbyNeko/Weather-Dashboard

### Deployed to:

https://abbyneko.github.io/Weather-Dashboard/

**Eat-Da-Burger** is an app that creates a list of burgers that can be added, deleted and moved to the list of Devoured burgers.

#### **Languages Used:**

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Handlebars, Bootstrap, Node.js, MySQL, Express

#### GitHub:

https://github.com/AbbyNeko/burger

### Deployed to:

https://enigmatic-hamlet-73997.herokuapp.com/

**Readable** is an app that allows you to save books to a reading, to read and currently reading book list.

### **Languages Used:**

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Google Books API

#### GitHub:

https://github.com/apeabody007/Readable

### Deployed to:

https://apeabody007.github.io/Readable/